穿这么帅要去哪里？
Wow! You look nice. What's the occasion?
莫妮卡和我要庆祝满十个月 我们在乔治法国餐厅订了位置
Monica and I are celebrating our 10-month anniversary.Got reservations at Jean-George.
你们怎么进得去？
How'd you get in?
打了几通电话，动用一些关系
Made a few calls,pulled some strings...
如果我们都吃鸡，不叫甜点 就让我们11：30进去吃
...and they'll seat us if we both have chicken and don't get dessert.
钱德 凯特琳，新发型喔
-Hi,Chandler. -Hey,Caitlin.Somebody got a haircut.
我恨死了，活像八岁小男孩
I hate it. I look like an 8-year-old boy.
如果真的是这样 那以前上体育课会有趣许多
If that was true,gym class would've been more interesting.
正好27美元 好，给你
-It's $27 even. -Okay. Here you go.
你养的鸡呢？
Where's the chicken?
在后头，被这鸭子气跑了
It's in the back. The duck pissed him off.
鸭子说先有蛋，才有鸡
He said that eggs came first.
谢了，下回见 好，再见
-Thanks. I'll see you later. -Bye.
你在干什么？ 怎么了？
What the hell was that?-What?
打情骂俏
-The flirting.
你不是正要去约会吗…跟谁来着…
Aren't you supposed to be going out with,let's see,
我妹妹
my sister?
我没在打情骂俏啊
I wasn't flirting.
那根本就是打情骂俏
It was totally flirting!
“新发型喔”
"Somebody got a haircut...."
好，首先 你模仿得很蹩脚
First of all,the impression? Uncanny.
第二，那不是打情骂俏 只是两个人闲话家常而已
Second,that wasn't flirting. That was just casual conversation.
哦，是哦
Yeah,right.
你要看打情骂俏？ 我示范给你看
You wanna see flirting? I'll show you.
不用了
I'm good.
本集播出：“罗斯不会调情”
The One Where Ross Can't Flirt
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
我真替乔伊感到骄傲
I am so proud of Joey.
他竟然要演“法律与秩序” 我知道
-He's gonna be on Law and Order! -I know.
可是你不觉得 叫“秩序与法律”比较对吗？
Don't you think it should be called Order and Law?
不对，要先把人抓起来再审问
No,because they arrest the guy and then try him.
别引着我说个没完了
Don't get me started on that.
我没在打情骂俏
-I was not flirting.
还在纪念日当天，丢脸！
-And on your anniversary. For shame!
怎么了？
What's going on?
钱德跟外送辣妹打情骂俏
He was hitting on the hot delivery girl.
我才没有，拜托你也小声点
I was not. And oh,God!
很抱歉，但有就是有
I'm sorry，but you were.
而且就算有谁要跟她搭讪 也应该是单身的男人
If anyone should be hitting on her...it's the guy who's single
也应该是有搞头的人嘛
...the guy who can do something about it.
看来有人想当披萨外送先生了
Sounds like someone wants to be Mr. Pizza Delivery Girl.
原来是这样？你喜欢凯特琳？
Is that what this is about? You like Caitlin?
罗斯，我们分手都两年了
Ross,we broke up two years ago.
中间你还结过婚
You've been married since then.
我们各自约会应该没问题吧
I think it's okay that we see other people.
我前几天在披萨店看到她
I was watching her at the pizza place.
她性感又风趣…
And she was just so sexy and funny
还有小巧可爱的…
and has the cutest little
三围不用说
We don't need her measurements.
意大利腊肠，意大利腊肠，意大利腊肠
Pepperoni,pepperoni,pepperoni.
罗斯，我知道她人美你喜欢 但她是不是蠢了点？
She's pretty and you love her,but is she stupid?
她忘了我点的素食披萨
She forgot my vegetarian.
太完美了
This is perfect.
她一定会回来送你的披萨
She'll have to come back here with your pizza.
到时我就展现出罗斯的魅力
And when she does,I will turn on the charm "au" Ross.
我真高兴你不吃肉
I am so glad you don't eat meat.
看吧，吃素对大家都好
See? Vegetarianism benefits everyone.
大家看是谁来了 还记得我祖母吗？
Hey,everybody,look who's here! You remember my grandmother.
好棒的一晚，太酷了
-Big night! -Yeah,it's so cool.
乔伊参与“法律与秩序”演出 你一定很骄傲吧
Joey on Law and Order. You must be proud.
钱德，她完全听不懂英文
She doesn't understand a word of English.
抱歉，我以为你是乔伊的另一个祖母
I thought you were Joey's other grandmother.
我又说英文了
I've done it again.
她是我的头号影迷
Nonnie's my biggest fan.
家族里只有她一个 从头到尾都相信我
She's the only one in the family who's always believed in me.
对，他是大明星 我的胖胖大明星
Si. Big star.My big fat Joey star.
对，我出生时有27磅，所以…
Yeah,I weighed,like,27 pounds when I was born.
纪念日快乐
-Happy anniversary!
十个月纪念日快乐
-Happy anniversary,10 months.
我刚才在淋浴的时候 想起我们在伦敦的第一晚
In the shower I was thinking about our first night in London.
乔伊的祖母来了
Joey's grandmother's right there.
会说英文的那个？
-The one who speaks English?
不会的那个
-The one who doesn't.
那晚你给我的爱真是火热
That was some hot love you gave me.
我去准备一下 不如戴我送你的耳环？
-I'll get ready. -Wear those earrings I got you.
好主意，就是要留到特别场合 好
That's a great idea. I was saving them for something special.
你得回家去
-You've got to go home.
但是我喜欢这里啊
-But I like it here.
你得回家拿我借给你的耳环 钱德要我今晚戴那副耳环
Get the earrings you borrowed. He wants me to wear them.
好，应该是放在我皮包里
I think they're in my purse.
你去穿衣服，我去找 好
Go get dressed and I'll look for them.
瑞秋，我要拿回我借给你的耳环
I need those earrings you borrowed.
好，我马上回来
Yeah,I'll be right back.
菲比，你会说意大利文？
Phoebe,you speak ltalian?
我猜是吧
I guess so.
来，谢谢你
-Here you go. -Thanks.
瑞秋，等等，另外一个呢？
Where's the other one?
你两个都要？
Oh,what,you want both of them?
会不会太贪心了？你觉得呢？
That's a little greedy,don't you think?
瑞秋格林，另一个耳环呢？
Rachel Karen Greene,where's the other one?
好啦，你先别生气
Look,just don't freak out,
好像不见了 还在公寓里，但一定不见了
but I kind of lost it.I know it's in the apartment,but I definitely lost it.
那我要怎么跟莫妮卡说？ 她今晚就要戴
What'll I tell Monica? She wants to wear them tonight.
叫她戴自己的耳环 这就是她的耳环
-Tell her to wear her own earrings. -These are her earrings.
不会吧…
No，No
你把莫妮卡的耳环借给我？ 她不允许我借她的东西耶
You lent me her earrings? I'm not allowed to borrow her stuff!
为什么？ 因为我都会弄丢
-Why not? -Because I lose her stuff!
看到那个盲人了吗？
You see that blind guy?
我等一下会痛打他一顿
I'm gonna bash his head in later.
我的主戏就快来了 主戏就快来了
My big scene's coming up. The big scene coming up.
若你说“大利马豆像泡泡一样升起” 她会不会比较懂？
If you said,"Big lima bean bubbling up," would she know the difference?
瑞秋，你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
我不敢看，太恐怖了
Oh,I just can't watch. It's too scary.
现在是尿布广告
It's a diaper commercial.
你知道我的 小孩啊，责任，吓死人
Yeah,well,you know me. Babies,responsibilities....
披萨外送
-Pizza delivery.
我来了，我来拿
-I'll get it! I will get that!
我的发型如何？
How does my hair look?
罗斯，你从96年就没变过了
Ross,it hasn't moved since 1996.
一个素食披萨
One vegetarian pizza.
12.5美元
It's 12.50.
对了，为了让你心里好过些 我想说我正好很喜欢八岁男孩
By the way,if it makes you feel any better I happen to like 8-year-old boys.
什么？
What?
我是说…之前你说过
Your hair. Before. Your hair.
你的发型很像八岁男孩
You said you thought your hair looked like an 8-year-old boy's...
我说我很喜欢…
...and I'm just saying I like it.
你的发型
The hair.
谢谢
Thanks.
你要明白，我不是真的喜欢八岁男孩
You understand,I don't actually like 8-year-old boys.
我在等你付钱
All I'm looking for is the money.
给你
Here you go.
别再帮我们送披萨了 我都快哭了
Stop bringing us pizzas,you.I'm gonna try.
不客气
You're welcome.
你就是不想看我得手，对吧？
You couldn't let me have her,could you?
什么？
What？
我真的很喜欢这个女孩 你干嘛要来凑热闹？
This is a girl I really like,and you had to swoop in there!
怎么了？
What?
钱德冲着外送辣妹打情骂俏
Chandler was flirting with the hot delivery girl.
真是多谢你了
Thank you for that.
我没有打情骂俏
I was not flirting.
没关系，我不在意，无所谓
It's okay. I don't care. That's fine.
真的？ 真的？
Really? Really？
又不是什么大事，我也经常这样
It's no big deal. I do it all the time.
你经常跟人打情骂俏？
You flirt with guys all the time?
是啊，那又不代表什么 你不是也没别的意思嘛
It doesn't mean anything. Just like it doesn't mean anything with you.
对，但是有一点很不一样 你比我辣多了
There's a difference. You're a lot hotter than I am.
这是真的
True story.
钱德，你真的介意？
This actually bothers you?
对，我是介意 我想很多人都会介意
Yes,and I think it'd bother a lot of people.
瑞秋，你和罗斯在一起那时
When you and Ross dated...
他跟别的女人打情骂俏 你会不会介意？
...did it bother you when he flirted with other women?
不会…他跟别的女人上床 我才会介意
No,it bothered me when he slept with other women.
真是多谢了
And thank you for that.
但其实我没啥好担心的 罗斯从来就不太会打情骂俏
I never had to worry.He was never good at the flirting thing.
什么？
What？
你在说什么？对你不就有效吗
What are you talking about? It worked with you.
你说的真是对极了
No,you're right.
我们认识，你对我打情骂俏 九年后你终于追到我了
We met,you flirted and then bam! Nine years later,you had me.
好…即然这样
All right.
我再来点个披萨 等凯特琳来的时候
You know what I'll do? I'll order another pizza.And when Caitlin gets here
我就来让你们见识一下 我有多会打情骂俏
...I will show you how well I flirt.
我还能要到她的电话号码
I will get her phone number.
不是披萨店的电话
And not the one on the menu.
我找到了
-I found it.
谢天谢地，在哪里找到的？
-Thank God! Where was it?
在你的梳妆台上
On your dresser.
那是原来的那一个
Okay,that is the one we already have.
我的主戏到了，就是现在
Here's my big scene. My big scene's here.
想不想打赌这事没有人听见？-我不跟你赌
-Wanna bet nobody heard anything? -No bet.
有人在吗？
Anybody home?
天啊
-Oh,my God.
怎么了？
-What?
大家继续笑
Everybody keep smiling.
我祖母发现一定会难过到死掉
It'll kill my grandmother if she finds out.
怎么了？
What is it?
我那一段被剪掉了
They cut me out of the show.
什么？
What?
你确定？
-Are you sure?
或许现在才轮到你上
-Maybe your scene's coming up.
不太可能 看到那个装尸体的袋子没？
Not likely. Because you see that body bag right there?
有啊 我在里面
Yes. -I'm in it.
太糟糕了，你要怎么办？
This is terrible. What'll you do?
不知道
I don't know.
这个小妇人活着 就是为了看我演戏
This little old lady lives for my career.
上回“我们的日子”不要我 她差点难过到死掉
When they dumped me off Days of Our Lives,she almost died.
那样很不妙
That's not good.
我们还找了个 特别看护来照顾她
-Yeah,we had to get her a home nurse.
天啊
-Oh,my God.
她差点死掉 还花了我们好多钱
Yeah,she almost died and got really expensive.
别用那种表情，大家继续笑…
You're not smiling. Not that face! Everybody smile!
乔伊，你怎么不实话实说？ 那又不能怪你
Just tell her what happened. It's not your fault.
如果我们继续这样说话 会不会吓到她？
If we keep talking this way,won't we freak her out soon?
很快…马上就轮我上场了
Soon. I'm gonna be on soon.
那就是我！
There I am!
萨姆·沃特森！
Sam Waterston!
不对…那是我…
No,no. That's me. That's me!
不是，那是萨姆·沃特森
No. Sam Waterston.
“爱与罪” “摩羯星一号”
Crime Misdemeanor,Capricorn One.
她听不懂“你好” 却知道“摩羯星一号”
She doesn't know "hello," but she knows Capricorn One.
菲比，我要那副耳环 节目一演完我们就要出去
I need those earrings. We're leaving when the show's over.
可是我已经还你了啊
But I already gave them back to you.
才没有
No,you didn't.
好，我已经还没还给你 我就是这样说的啊
I already didn't gave them back to you. That's what I said.
另一个耳环在哪里？
Where's that other earring?
菲比，不在这里…
It's not here,Phoebe. It's not here.
我昨晚有去钱德和乔伊那里
I went to Chandler's last night.
好，记得要检查钱德的珠宝盒
Make sure you check Chandler's jewelry box.
慢着，钱德有珠宝盒？
Chandler has a jewelry box?
好了，我们只有十分钟 你要我现在就跟你解释吗？
We have 10 minutes. Do you want me to get into that now?
菲比，那个素食披萨… 你吃得还习惯吗？
Hey,Phoebe.How's that vegetarian pizza working out for you?
你和那些蔬菜 还真是有两下子，是吧？
You and those vegetables have a real...thing going on,huh?
你干嘛怪里怪气的？
Why are you being weird?
你喜不喜欢？
Do you like it?
不喜欢，否则我就会问 “你干嘛这么可爱”了
No. That'd be,"Why are you being cute?"
好吧，我在练习打情骂俏
Okay. I'm working on my flirting.
哦，我没看出来
I did not get that.
莫妮卡，你喜欢看 “法律与秩序”吗？
So,Monica,do you like Law and Order?
喜欢，很好看
Yeah,it's good.
我发现了你一些新的事情
I found out all this stuff about you.
好比你爱看“法律与秩序”
You like Law and Order...
还有你到处跟人打情骂俏
...and you've flirted with every guy in the tri-state area.
好，我问你 你可以打情骂俏，我却不行
Okay,let me get this straight.It's okay for you to flirt,but not for me?
真高兴我们把话说清楚了
I'm glad we cleared that up.
抱歉，但男女有些事是不一样的
I'm sorry,but some things are different for men and women.
继续，教教我一些男女的差别
Go on ，Teach me about men and women.
好，虽然我已经教过你很多了
I've already taught you so much already,but whatever.
你跟男人打情骂俏的时候
When you flirt with a guy,
你觉得没什么
you think,"No big deal."
但对方会觉得 他终于找到人上床了
But he thinks,"Finally! Somebody who wants to sleep with me."
不可能 这是真的
-No way! -It's true.
真可悲 这也是真的
-Well,that's pathetic. -Again,true.
男人都这样吗？
-This goes for all guys?
醒着的男人都适用
-All guys that are awake.
等我们上床睡觉后
We go to sleep.
世界另一边的男人起床 继续做一模一样的事
All guys from the other end of the world wake up and act the same way.
好，又进广告了 我还是没跟她说
It's another commercial and I still haven't told her.
乔伊，这是最后一段广告 你只剩十分钟了
Joey,this is the last commercial.You got 10 minutes left.
我知道…你要我怎么办？
-I know!What am I gonna do?
不许你逃跑，留她在这里
You will not run out and leave her here.
对，好啦
Yeah,all right.
乔伊？
Joey
乔伊马上回来
Joey's gonna be right back.
马上回来？
Right back?
我们顺便来聊聊你吧
Meanwhile,let's talk about you.
你年纪大，个子小
So you're old and small.
找到没？
-Did you find it?
耳环是没有，但我在沙发底下 找到我的太阳眼镜
-The earring,no.But I found my sunglasses.
我从去年夏天找到现在
I've been looking for these since last summer.
那是我借给你的太阳眼镜
Those are mine. You borrowed them from me.
好，别激动，还你就是了
Okay. Calm down. Here they are.
菲比
Phoebe
我们要怎么办？ 我不知道…
-What do we do? -I don't know. I don't know!
我们只好老实跟莫妮卡说了
We'll just have to tell Monica,that's all.
老天，她一定会杀了我
Oh,God! She's gonna kill me.
我可以跟她说是我弄掉的
I could tell her it was all my fault.
那就太好了
Oh,that'd be great.
莫妮卡，我有话要跟你说
Mon,could I talk to you?
好，什么事？
Yeah. What is it?
我弄丢了你一支耳环 对不起，我真的很抱歉
I lost one of your earrings.I'm sorry. I am so,so sorry.
好吧，都弄丢了还能怎样
All right,what can you do? If you lost it,you lost it.
我保证会赔你一副新的 我真的很愧疚
I'll replace it. I promise. I feel so terrible.
没关系，你又不是故意的
That's fine. You didn't do it on purpose.
瞧你难过的，来
Look at you. Come here.
好点了没？ 有啊，你最棒了
-You feel better? -Yeah. You're the best.
好，等一等
Okay,wait a minute.
我不能这样
I can't do this.
其实不是菲比弄丢的
Listen,honey,it's not Phoebe's fault.
她把你的耳环借我 是我弄丢的，我真的很抱歉
She lent me the earrings.I lost it. I'm so sorry,
亲爱的，我也觉得好愧疚
honey. I feel terrible too.
所以我才不借给你东西！
That is exactly why I do not lend you stuff!
先是我的首饰
First,my jewelry.
不是首饰，就是我的蓝色毛衣
If it's not that,it's my sweater.
不是蓝色毛衣 就是我的太阳眼镜
And if it's not that,it's my sunglasses.
你的太阳眼镜？ 对！
Your sunglasses? -Yes
对耶
Oh,right.
披萨外送 我的！…
-Pizza. -Mine,mine,mine!
好，要开始了
Okay,here goes.
准备见识一流的打情骂俏
Prepare yourselves for some class-A flirting.
等等…
Okay,hold on.
准备好了
Okay
你不用证明什么
Honey，you have nothing to prove
若你真的喜欢这个女孩 我不觉得打情骂俏是好办法
If you really like this girl,I don't think flirting is the right way
等着看，好吧
You'll see. Okay
她叫什么名字？
What's her name?
凯特琳…
Caitlin!
凯特琳
Caitlin
这样吃下去也不是办法
We can't keep eating like this.
12.5美元
It's $12.50.
好
Okay
你们做披萨 是用烧木头的炉子吗？
Do you make the pizzas in one of those wood-burning ovens?
不是，其实是瓦斯炉
No,actually,I think they're gas.
瓦斯炉？
Gas?
真带劲
Intense.
如果盖勒家的人 都这样打情骂俏的话
If this is how all the Gellers flirt,
我们就没有问题了
we don't have a problem.
你知道瓦斯的味道吗？
You know that smell gas has?
知道
Yes
那是加进去的 什么？
They put that in. What？
瓦斯其实是无色无味
-The gas is odorless.
加上味道是为了让人 在瓦斯漏气时能闻得出来
But they add the smell so you know when there's a leak.
好吧
Well,okay.
很多气体都有味道…
A lot of other gas smells.
还有没有人性啊
Oh,the humanity!
甲烷有味道…
Methane smells....
不好意思，我真的得走了
You know what? Actually,I really should go.
我还没付钱呢
-But I haven't paid you yet.
没关系，你们点了那么多 这一个算我请的
-That's okay.You guys have ordered so many that this one's on me.
我是不是跟她说到瓦斯的事？
Was I talking to her about gas?
除了这个没别的了
More so than anything else.
我觉得很有意思
I found it interesting.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
不用…别担心
Don't worry about it.
九年之后 我和她就能在一起了
In nine years,she and l will be right there!
好，我去清掉这些披萨盒
I'm gonna clear out some of these boxes.
罗斯？ 怎么了？
Ross？ Yes？
还有哪些气体会加味道？
What else do they add smell to?
我是瑞秋
Hi,I'm Rachel.
住楼上的 叫一堆披萨的那家
The people with all the pizza.
披萨有问题吗？ 不是…披萨很好吃
Was there a problem?No,they're fine. Great pizza.
其实是我朋友罗斯的事
But,actually,my friend Ross...
他只要打情骂俏就会紧张
...he gets nervous when he's flirting.
天啊，他是在打情骂俏？ 没错
Oh,my God!That was flirting? -Yes
我知道你的感觉…
I know,I know.
不过一旦过了那个阶段
I'm telling you,once you get past that part...
那个让你想要自杀的阶段
...where it feels like you wanna die...
你就会发现他是个大好人
...he's a really good person.
开口闭口都是瓦斯的那个人？
The guy with the gas?
我要告诉你他真的很体贴风趣
I'm telling you,he's really sweet and really funny...
还有一副好心肠
...and he's just got a good heart.
其实我觉得他蛮可爱的 可是一开始说话就…
You know,actually,I did think that he was cute and then he started talking.
这就对了…
See,there you go.
而且我觉得他很喜欢你 真的吗？
-Besides,I think he really likes you. -Really?
我们七个人，却叫了十个披萨 这还不够明显吗？
Well,we have seven people and 10 pizzas. What do you think?
我以为是因为乔伊很能吃
I thought Joey was there.
罗斯值得你去试试看
Yeah,no,but just I'm telling you he's worth a shot.
如果他那么棒 你怎么不去跟他约会？
Well,if he's so great why don't you go out with him?
你知道吗？
Well,you know,
对于这一点 我们可能需要好好聊一聊
at some point...you and I may need to have a longer conversation.
罗斯？
Hey,Ross?
我刚才在走廊遇到凯特琳
I just ran into Caitlin in the hallway.
你打情骂俏的技巧 肯定比我想像中更高明
You must be getting better at this flirting stuff than I thought.
什么意思？
-What do you mean?
虽然我搞不懂 但她要我转交她的电话给你
-I don't get it,but she wanted me...to give you her number.
她自己给你的？ 是啊
And she just gave you this? Yes
瑞秋，谢了 但我不需要你帮忙
Rach,thanks. But I don't need you doing me any favors.
我没帮忙啊，是她觉得你可爱
I didn't. She thought you were cute.
这点我倒是相信
Well,that I can believe.
还在演吗？
Hey,is the show still on?
快要演完了  嘿，纳妮
Almost over,man.  Hey，Nonnie
那是教皇吗？
Is that the pope?
我干嘛要看？
Why am I looking?
来了，我的主戏上场
Oh,here I am! This is my big scene.
快退后
All right,back off!
我有枪喔
I got a gun!
用起来可不会手软
I'm not afraid to use it.
是乔伊！ 没错，纳妮
Joey！ That's right,Nonnie.
你起码也该换一件上衣的
You couldn't have at least changed your shirt?
我要你在手提箱里 装满十万美元…
Now,I want a suitcase filled with $ 100,000
装满十万美元的小钞
Filled with $ 100,000 in small bills.
若是我没拿到…
And if I don't get Shoo!
And if I don't get it...
我就毙了这支鸭子
...I'll shoot this duck!
不能这样
Oh,no!
我要出去了
I'm coming out!
她会相信吗？
And she's supposed to buy this?
乔伊，你太勇敢了！…
Joey，bravo…
地面控制队呼叫总部…
Ground control to Major Tom
倒数开始…
Commencing countdown
动力…
Engines
全开
On
这是下周的片段…下周的
That's scenes from next week's show. Next week.
我一定要等着看
I am definitely gonna watch that.
这一副看起来一样吗？
Do these look the same?
一模一样
-Definitely.
左右一起看 那就不一样了
-Not as each other.Then,no.
准备好了吗？ 是的
-Hey,you ready? -Yeah.
你真美
You look amazing.
我是全世界最幸运的男人
I'm the luckiest man in the world.
你即将要更幸运了
You're about to get a little luckier.
耳环让我看看
-Let me see the earrings.
耳环…
-Right,the earrings.
好看极了
They look great.
你男友的品味真是一流吧
Does your boyfriend have the best taste or what?
我男友的品味真的很棒
My boyfriend really does have great taste.
多谢你帮我选耳环
Thanks for picking out the earrings.